http://www.iac.org/legal-notices

Skip to main content
Main menu
HomeJoin or RenewWhere to Begin >Getting StartedRecreationalThe Aerobatic BoxAerobatic SchoolsCommon QuestionsAerobatic FiguresPrograms >Local Chapters >OverviewChapter LocatorChapter ResourcesJudges >School CalendarCoursesHosting a SchoolExamsAwardsCollegiate >RulesSchoolsResultsInsuranceSafety >TechWatchSafety AlertsResourcesGovt Liaison >OverviewWaiversScholarshipsCompetition >OverviewChapter Contests >Contest CalendarResultsRules >Get RulebookRule ChangesU.S. NationalsU.S. TeamsSupporting InfoRegional Series >InformationResultsNATIONALSAirVentureMedia >In the Loop NewslettersGalleriesVideosArchives >Governance DocsArticlesWebinarsTechnical TipsHall of FameUS Team HistoryLinksAbout >Who We AreSite FAQsLeadershipGovernance DocsReport a ProblemContact UsAdvertisingBrandingLegal NoticesCreditsShopGive
Disclaimer • Permission to Use • Privacy Policy • Terms of Use
Disclaimer
The name of "Experimenal Aircraft Association" or "EAA" or "EAA Aviation Foundation" or "IAC" or "International Aerobatic Club" may not be used in advertising or publicity pertaining to distribution of this information without specific, written prior permission. EAA, the EAA Aviation Foundation, and IAC make no representations about the suitability of this information for any purpose. It is provided "as is" without express or implied warranty.
EAA, the EAA Aviation Foundation, and IAC disclaim all warranties with regard to this information, including all implied warranties of merchantability and fitness. In no event shall EAA and the EAA Aviation Foundation be liable for any special, indirect or consequential damages or any damages whatsoever resulting from loss of use, data or profits, whether in an action of contract, negligence or other action, arising out of or in connection with the use or performance of this information.
Permission to Use
Permission to use, copy and distribute documents delivered from this Worldwide Web server and related graphics is hereby granted, provided that both the disclaimer notice above and this permission notice appear. All other rights reserved.
Privacy Policy
What information do we collect?
Visitors to this website who have JavaScript enabled are tracked using Google Analytics. The information collected and/or derived by Google Analytics includes, but is not necessarily limited to:
Type of web browser (or other user agent) used, including version number
Type of operating system
Screen resolution
Number of screen colors supported
JavaScript support
Flash version
Network location and IP address (can be used to determine your approximate geographic location)
Hostname
Internet connection speed
Time of visit
Pages visited
Time spent on each page
Referring site statistics
The website (URI) you came through in order to arrive at this website
Search engine query used (example: typing in a phrase into a search engine like Google, and clicking on a link from that search engine)
If you use our contact form, we will retain your email address.
We store the following data for each IAC member account:
Name
Contact information
Phone number
Email address
Mailing address
EAA number
IAC number
Membership expiration date
This site DOES NOT store:
Social Security Numbers
Bank account numbers
Credit card numbers
Birthdates
What do we use your information for?
We use the information we collect to better understand our site visitors, and to improve our website.
Do we use cookies?
Yes. (Cookies are small files that a site transfers to your computer's hard drive through your Web browser -- if you have configured the browser to do so -- which enable the site to recognize your browser and capture and remember certain information.) We use cookies to compile aggregate data about site traffic and site interaction so that we can offer better site experiences in the future. We may contract with third-party service providers to assist us in better understanding our site visitors. These service providers are not permitted to use the information collected on our behalf except to help us conduct and improve our business.
Do we disclose any information to outside parties?
We do not sell, trade, or otherwise disclose your personally identifiable information to outside parties, except as follows:
To third parties who assist us in operating our website, conducting our business, or servicing you, so long as those parties agree to keep this information confidential.
We may release contact information for IAC members who volunteer for tasks that involve being available with other members or the public, such as hosting a judges school or serving on a committee.
We may also release your information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our site policies, or protect ours or others rights, property, or safety.
Third party links
Occasionally, at our discretion, we may incorporate links to third party websites on our website. These third party sites have separate and independent privacy policies. We therefore have no responsibility or liability for the content and activities of these linked sites. Nonetheless, we seek to protect the integrity of our site and welcome any feedback about these sites.
California Online Privacy Protection Act Compliance
Because we value your privacy we have taken the necessary precautions to be in compliance with the California Online Privacy Protection Act. We therefore will not distribute your personal information to outside parties without your consent. As part of the California Online Privacy Protection Act, all users of our site may make any changes to their information at anytime by logging in and clicking on the 'My account' link.
Childrens Online Privacy Protection Act Compliance
We are in compliance with the requirements of COPPA (Childrens Online Privacy Protection Act), we do not collect any information from anyone under 13 years of age. Our website, products and services are all directed to people who are at least 13 years old or older.
Your Consent
By using our site, you consent to the terms of this privacy policy.
Effective Date
This policy was last modified on 2/9/2015, and is effective from that date forward.
Terms of USE
In consideration of your use of this site, you represent that you are of legal age to form a binding contract and are not a person barred from receiving services under the laws of the United States or other applicable jurisdiction. You agree to provide true, accurate, current and complete information about yourself upon registration and thereafter. You are responsible for maintaining the confidentiality of your password and account, and are fully responsible for all activities that occur under your password or account. You agree to immediately notify us of any unauthorized use of your password or account or any other breach of security.  IAC cannot and will not be liable for any loss or damage arising from your failure to comply with this Section. You agree to comply with all local rules regarding online conduct and acceptable Content, including all applicable laws regarding the transmission of technical data exported from the United States or the country in which you reside.
You further agree not to use this web site:
upload, post, email, transmit or otherwise make available (“Post”) any content:
that is unlawful, harmful, threatening, abusive, harassing, tortious, defamatory, vulgar, obscene, libelous, false or inaccurate, invasive of another’s privacy, hateful, or racially, ethnically or otherwise objectionable;
that you do not have a right to make available under any law or under contractual or fiduciary relationships (such as inside information, proprietary and confidential information learned or disclosed as part of employment relationships or under nondisclosure agreements); or
that infringes any patent, trademark, trade secret, copyright or other proprietary rights (“Rights”) of any party;
harm minors in any way;
impersonate any person or entity, or falsely state or otherwise misrepresent your affiliation with a person or entity;
Post any unsolicited or unauthorized advertising, promotional materials, “junk mail,” “spam,” “chain letters,” “pyramid schemes,” or any other form of solicitation;
Post any material that contains software viruses or any other computer code, files or programs designed to interrupt, destroy or limit the functionality of any computer software or hardware or telecommunications equipment;
interfere with or disrupt the site or servers or networks connected to the site, or disobey any requirements, procedures, policies or regulations of networks connected to the site;
violate any applicable local, state, national or international law, intentionally or unintentionally;
“stalk” or otherwise harass another; and/or
collect or store personal data about other users.
You agree to be fully responsible for your own content. The site acts as a venue for you to post your content. While we have the right to refuse to post or remove, edit or abridge any content for any reason, we are otherwise not involved in the writing or decisions as to the content posted by our users. As a result, we have no control over the quality, accuracy or legality of the content on the site. All content posted on the site is the sole responsibility of the person from whom such content originated. Because the site is a venue, in the event that you have a dispute with the site or a user of the site, you release IAC and its officers, directors, members and employees from claims, demands and damages (actual and consequential) of every kind and nature, known and unknown, suspected and unsuspected, disclosed and undisclosed, arising out of or in any way connected with such disputes.
You agree to indemnify and hold IAC and its officers, directors, members and/or employees harmless from any claims, damages, losses or costs (including reasonable attorney’s fees) that arise out of any of your Content, including, without limitation, any Content posted or otherwise provided by you that infringes any copyright, trademark, intellectual property right of any person or defames any person or violates any person’s rights of publicity or privacy, or otherwise violates these Terms of Use.
Member Login
Upcoming Events
Other: EAA Hall of Fame Banquet, 2021-03-25 17:00 to 21:00
Meeting: IAC Annual Membership Meeting July 30, 2021-07-30 07:30 to 19:00
